<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Wren Howell</title>
    <link>https://wrentarohowell.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Wren Howell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wrentarohowell.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Naunced View on Web3</title>
      <link>https://wrentarohowell.com/blog/a-naunced-view-web3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wrentarohowell.com/blog/a-naunced-view-web3/</guid>
      <description>As I reflected on my journey into tech, I realized that my motivations and interests are linked to liberation. Liberation is why I studied the Civil Rights Movement, why I was interested in history, and why I got into cybersecurity and tech. I have been in plenty of Web3 Twitter spaces over the last couple of weeks, and I often hear that Web3 is revolutionary because it has the potential to liberate people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Flags to Look for When Looking for a New Team</title>
      <link>https://wrentarohowell.com/blog/red-flags/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wrentarohowell.com/blog/red-flags/</guid>
      <description>It is a new year with a competitive job market and plenty of people looking for new roles. Recently, I was in a Twitter space where participants and I talked about red flags to look for when joining a new team. The following are a few we identified when looking for a new team. In no particular order, here they are.
 Managers that do not have technical experience.  This applies to people who are relatively early in their careers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My journey into the tech field</title>
      <link>https://wrentarohowell.com/blog/my-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wrentarohowell.com/blog/my-journey/</guid>
      <description>I have been in the tech field for almost two years, and a common question that I get asked from college students and high school students that look like me is, “How did you get there?” So to all that ask, here is my story.
If someone had asked me when I was in high school that I would be working in tech, I would not have believed them. Back then, I did not even know that was a career option.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
